

## **ABOUT ME**

I am a 22-year-old passionate about developing web solutions. I consider myself a productive and diligent person when it comes to the challenges that arise. I strive to perfect my projects once completed and never cease to acquire new knowledge.

#### CONTACT



54 11 4174-0902



Villa Devoto, CABA.



grinmatias@gmail.com



grinmatias.com.ar



github.com/Zeta2003x



Salesforce trailblazer profile



bit.ly/MGrinLkin

## **CERTIFICACIONES**

Platform App Builder

Agentforce Specialist

**AWS CCP** 

## **LANGUAGE**

Native Spanish Advanced English (C2) Conversational Italian

# **GRIN MATÍAS**

#### Salesforce Developer

With expertise primarily in Apex, LWC, Python, Javascript, Excel, and Power BI.

## **SKILLS**

- Salesforce (Apex LWC Flows)
- HTML CSS Node React
- · C Git SQL UML
- · Python (Selenium Flask Pandas)
- · Power Bi Word PowerPoint
- · Excel (Power Query VBA)

#### **WORK EXPERIENCE**

#### Salesforce Developer - Endava

September 2023 - Present

Development and administration in Salesforce, programming in Apex, Lightning Web Components and Flows. Projects in multiple verticals (Insurance, Finance and HR). User and permissions management, reports and dashboards, AI (Agentforce, Prompt Builder and ChatGPT integrations).

#### **Data Analyst - Symmetria**

April - August 2023

Data analysis and reporting in Power BI.

Production planning and control.

Development of a management system in Excel and Visual Basic.

Technical support.

## Tech Support - Estudio Grin Bonomo y Asociados

October 2019 - March 2023

Web scraping and process automation with Python and Selenium. Creation of reports in Power BI.

Analysis and data entry of information related to incident reports.

## **EDUCATION**

## **UTN-FRBA**, Buenos Aires - Arg

Information Systems Engineering 2021 - Present

## Colegio Cardenal Copello, Buenos Aires - Arg

High School Studies 2016 - 2020

## San Francisco College, Buenos Aires - Arg

English Institute 2011 - 2020